<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- about us page english-->
<main date_updated="oct 19 2008">
<item swfName="about_image.swf">
	<headline>FAQ</headline>
	<copy>Q. What should I expect when I visit?
A. When you visit Mt. Zion, you can expect to feel welcomed and accepted into our local church family. You'll join with others as we worship God with passion and sincerity. At Mt. Zion, we believe in the power of the Word of God to transform lives, break mindsets, heal brokenness, restore wholeness, and empower people to live mature Christian lives. Our dedicated staff is committed to ministering the life-giving power of Christ to you and your family. It is our desire as a ministry to truly help you experience the best of life.

Q. What does Mt. Zion offer my family?
A. At Mt. Zion, we believe in the importance of meeting people at their point of need in life. As such, we've designed our ministry outlets to connect people of all ages, developmental stages, and backgrounds with one another. We believe in building successful families. Our family ministry supports parents with children from childbirth through the teenage years. During most service times, we have programs designed to meet the developmental and spiritual needs of your children, infant through fifth grade, with creative activities and lessons. Our student ministry, grades 6-12, has their own age-appropriate service on Sunday, Wednesday and Saturday evenings, with a hangout following the Saturday service.

Q. What are Mt. Zion 's service times?
A. On Sunday mornings, we offer three identical morning services: 8:00am, 9:30am and 11:15am. All Sunday morning services simultaneously run with our Children's Ministry program for infants through fifth grade. The following programs/classes are offered at the main church campus on Sundays at 6:00PM:  our Spanish-speaking service (English translation provided), Bible Training, Counselor Training, Student Ministry service, and our Children's Ministry program. Also on Sundays at 6:00pm, Generation One young adult services are held at The District. On Mondays at the main church campus at 7:00pm, we offer Counselor Training and the New Testament Class.  Also on Mondays at 7:30pm, we host our Life Enrichment Program at The District. On Tuesdays at the main church campus at 10:00am, we hold a Miracle Healing Service and at 7:30pm, Pastor Loren teaches on The Kingdom of God and His Church.  Also on Tuesdays at 7:30pm, we host our Life Enrichment Program at The District.  Wednesdays at 7:30PM, we have our mid-week Holy Spirit Apostilic service, Student Ministry service, and our Children's Ministry program at the main church.  Thursdays at 7:30pm, we host our Life Enrichment Program and Managing Our Finances God's Way at The District.  Saturdays at the main church campus at 10:00am, we hold a Lord's Prayer Service.  Also on Saturdays at 6:00pm, a Student Ministry service/hangout is held at the Waterford Christian Association.

Q. What is the television and radio broadcast schedule?
A. TELEVISION BROADCAST -

Canal de la Fe- Ch. 17
San Salvador, El Salvador
	
9:00AM LT

RADIO BROADCAST -
Monday - Friday
	103.5FM WMUZ-Detroit
	10:00AM EST
	& 9:15PM EST

Grupo Pacifico Television & Radio Station
Lima, Peru

Q. How do I locate Mt. Zion ?
If you are traveling northbound on I-75.
Take I-75 North to Exit 84 ( Baldwin Road ).
Turn Right (North) onto Baldwin Road.
Take Baldwin Road North 1 mile, until you reach Maybee Road.
Turn Left (West) onto Maybee Road.
Take Maybee Road approximately 1.5 miles until you reach Mt. Zion.
Mt. Zion is on the left.

If you are traveling southbound on I-75.
Take I-75 South to Exit 89 ( Sashabaw Road ).
Turn Right (South) onto Sashabaw Road.
Turn Left (East) onto Waldon Road ( Waldon Road is the first,
 intersection once you are on Sashabaw Road ).
Take Waldon Road east until you reach Clintonville Road.
Turn Right (South) onto Clintonville Road.
Take Clintonville Road south until you reach Maybee Road,
 ( Maybee Road is immediately before the I-75 overpass).
Turn Left onto Maybee Road.
Mt. Zion is on the right.

Q. How do I get connected?
A. Mt. Zion provides many opportunities for you and your family to "get connected" to the heart of our church, to our extensive church family, and to areas that might be of interest to you. Because of this, we provide many ministry opportunities to do just that. One point of connection to the ministry of Mt. Zion is through our small group ministry. Our Small Groups are located throughout the metro-Detroit area and are designed to connect people on a more intimate level. Even though we are a large church, we desire for everyone, at every stage of life, to feel connected and find his or her purpose in life. Click here for a listing of small groups in your area.

Q. How do I feel "at home" in the church?
A. Everyone wants to have a sense of belonging in life. At Mt. Zion, we believe wholeheartedly that having a strong sense of community is key to experiencing the best of life. There are a few steps you can take to ensure that you'll feel "at home" here:

•  Regularly attend services - When you regularly attend services, you'll be enriched and strengthened spiritually. In addition, you'll become familiar with friendly faces that would love to meet you and make you feel welcome here.

•  Connect yourself in a ministry - In a large church, it's easy to get "lost in the shuffle." That's why we offer many ministries that will help you connect to the core of who we are. Additionally, our small group ministry is dedicated to connecting you to other Christians in a much smaller, more personal setting. Enjoy food, fellowship, and an opportunity to form lasting relationships in any of our small groups.

•  Join the ministry team as a volunteer - Join the ministry team as a volunteer - Do you want to grab hold of the heartbeat of our ministry and make an impact in the lives of other people? If so, we need you! Building a great church requires great people like you in order to succeed. Volunteering your time and talents can be one of the most rewarding experiences you'll have in life.   
</copy>
</item>
</main>