<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- about us page english-->
<main date_updated="oct 19 2008">
<item swfName="about_image.swf">
	<headline>Pastor Loren Covarrubias</headline>
	<copy>	Loren Covarrubias is the third of nine children born to Bill and Jean Covarrubias. He was born and raised in Clarkston, Michigan. At a very young age, Pastor Loren gave his life to the Lord and has served Him faithfully ever since. As a young adult, feeling a call to ministry on his life, Loren began attending Ministers Candidate School at Bethesda Missionary Temple in Detroit, Michigan under the direction of Patricia Beall Gruits. During this time of preparation, Pastor Loren's mother began a small Bible study in the basement of their home. Upon completion of Minister's Candidate school in 1978, Pastor Loren began shepherding the Bible study group and over a short period of time Mt. Zion Church was birthed with a handful of people who were dedicated to the vision that the Lord gave Pastor Loren: "I will make you a vessel of new wine and I will give you a people that out of their midst shall flow the wine of the Lord, multiplication and increase, multiplication and increase."

	In 1980, Pastor Loren married Bonnie Groth. Bonnie's contagious faith, her love for the Lord and gift of singing gave the two of them an awesome ministry together. With Pastor Loren preaching the Word and Bonnie leading praise and worship, they began to see exponential growth over the next few years. During the growth of the church, Pastor Loren and Bonnie had three beautiful children: Loren, Billy, and Ashley. Their children are now young adults and actively involved at Mt. Zion.

	Pastor Loren has authored two books, About Fathers House, and his newly released, Discovering Favor with God (October 2004). Today, he is the host of the 'It's a New Day!' television and radio program, which airs on an international level. The Spanish-speaking version of the program, 'Es un Dia Nuevo!' is now being aired in Central and South America to millions more people.

	Pastor Loren is looking to the future and preparing once again for a great move of God. Construction is now underway for a brand-new ministry complex, which will house a 3,800-seat main auditorium, 400-seat theatre, new office center, as well as classroom facilities.

	Pastor Loren's vision is for Mt. Zion to be a visible expression of Jesus Christ in the community and world by proclaiming, demonstrating and discipling people in the word of God. </copy>
</item>
</main>